wajas.com 2009-06-21

# Privacy Policy :: Waja Madness!

###### Wajas.com » Privacy Policy

**ERROR:** You must login to view the page you are trying to access. 

If you were logged in and have been inactive for a while - you have been automatically logged out for your security and you will need to login again. Thank you.  
  
---  
  
This privacy policy sets out how Wajas uses and protects any information that you provide upon registration and use of this site.

Wajas guarantees that your privacy will be protected and should we ask that you provide any information it will be used for this site and only this site. Your information will not be distributed, leased, or sold to third parties unless required by law.

**What we collect and why:**

  * Email address for confirming account registration and any notices/alerts that may get sent out.
  * IP Address for tracking users within the site.
  * Cookies for User's account information.
  * Any information pertaining to surveys or polls to better our site/service.
  * Paypal email when buying our goods. The emails are not saved or recorded; we just need the email in order to verify you paid.

**Links to other sites:**

Many links may be found within our site so note that when you click the link and leave Wajas, we have no control over that site. We cannot be held responsible for any content, or information you provide to another site as it has no connection to Wajas and, there for, might not follow our Privacy Statement or Rules.

Wajas may change this privacy policy any time in the future, so please check it frequently. This policy is effective from November 21, 2006.
